semaphoreci.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Semaphore

Last updated: May 18, 2018

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Rendered Text collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://semaphoreci.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Rendered Text on the Site.This Privacy Policy explains what information Rendered Text collects about Users, what we do with that information, how we share it, and how we handle the content Users place in our products and services. It also explains the choices available to Users regarding our use of User personal information and how Users can access and update this information.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address (required), name (optional), website (optional), company (optional), location (optional), gravatar. Further information may be required if users choose to purchase paid components of the Site, such as credit card and billing information. Site uses third party partners for credit card processing who may require and store your credit card and billing information. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies and tracking

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. By using our Site, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your computer or device. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. Site does not track your online browsing activity on other online services over time and we do not permit third-party services to track your activity on our site with the exception of:

Basic [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) tracking to get information about how people use the Site. See [Google Analytics’ privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html) to learn how they use this information. You can opt out [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

[Google Remarketing](https://www.google.rs/ads/innovations/remarketing.html) to show ads to Users who have previously visited our Site using cookies. Users can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Occasional User behavior tracking performed with Crazy Egg analytics tool. Read [Crazy Egg’s privacy policy](https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy) to learn how they use this information. You can opt out [here](https://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out).

Occasional User behavior tracking performed with Smartlook analytics tool. Read [Smartlook’s privacy policy](https://www.smartlook.com/privacy) to learn how they use this information. You can opt out [here](https://www.smartlook.com/opt-out).

Occasional User behavior tracking performed with Autopilot analytics tool. Read [Autopilot’s privacy policy](https://autopilothq.com/privacypolicy.html) to learn how they use this information. You can opt out by unsubscribing from emails.

Occasional User behavior tracking performed with Customer.io tool. Read [Customer.io’s privacy policy](https://customer.io/privacy-policy.html) to learn how they use this information. You can opt out by unsubscribing from emails.

## How we use collected information

Rendered Text collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To personalize User experience. We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To send periodic emails. The email address Users provide for notifications, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their notification settings. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * To provide services to our customers.
  * To maintain our accounts and records.
  * To enhance, modify, personalise or otherwise improve our services and communications for the benefit of our customers.
  * To promote our services through communications that we think will be of interest to you.
  * To undertake research.
  * To identify and prevent fraud.
  * To enhance the security of our network and information systems.
  * To understand how people interact with our websites.
  * To occasionally contact you for market research purposes.
  * To customise our website according to your interests.
  * To determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising.
  * To process your orders.
  * For statistical purposes and to improve the website and services we offer.

If, at any time, you would like to stop receiving these promotional e-mails, you may follow the opt-out instructions contained in any such e-mail. If you opt-out of receiving emails or promotions from us, we still may send you e-mail about your account, any Services you have requested or received from us, or for other customer-service purposes. Although opt-out requests are usually processed immediately, please allow ten (10) business days for a removal request to be processed.

## Users control over collected information

User can request a copy, correction or deletion of the personal information by emailing [support@semaphoreci.com](mailto:support@semaphoreci.com). Deleting the account will cause all the data in the account to be permanently deleted from our systems within a reasonable time period, as permitted by law and will disable your access to any other services that require an account. We will respond to any such request, and any appropriate request to access, correct, update or delete your personal information within the time period specified by law (if applicable) or without excessive delay. We will promptly fulfill requests to delete personal data unless the request is not technically feasible or such data is required to be retained by law (in which case we will block access to such data, if required by law).

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. We are committed to announcing any security breaches within 72 hours after we notice this kind of issue.

## Data storage, ransfer and security

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. The servers on which Personal Information is stored are kept in a controlled environment. While we take reasonable efforts to guard your personal information, no security system is impenetrable and due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. In addition, we cannot guarantee that any incidentally-collected Personal Information you choose to store in our Site are maintained at levels of protection to meet specific needs or obligations you may have relating to that information.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

## Third party website

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Rendered Text has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

Any questions about this policy should be addressed to Rendered Text, Svetozara Miletića 10, 21000 Novi Sad, Serbia, or by email at: [support@semaphoreci.com](mailto:support@semaphoreci.com).
